<resources>
    <string name="app_name">cc17-3f-perezja-act6</string>
    <string name="title">30 Days of Tech and Gaming Tips</string>
    <string name="day_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day_1_title">Budget-Friendly Gaming Rig</string>
    <string name="day_1_des">If you\'re on a budget, consider a pre-built gaming PC. Be mindful that PCs marketed as gaming PCs could be more expensive but may offer the same or similar components to a PC marketed as "office".</string>
    <string name="day_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day_2_title">Core Components Combo</string>
    <string name="day_2_des">Building a gaming rig from scratch doesn\'t have to break the bank. Consider looking at bundle options which include a motherboard and CPU.</string>
    <string name="day_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day_3_title">Choose the Right Fit</string>
    <string name="day_3_des">When building your own gaming PC, ensure you choose the right size case for your needs: full tower, mid-tower, or mini-ITX. For instance, a standard ATX motherboard may not fit into a mini-ITX case.</string>
    <string name="day_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day_4_title">Speed vs. Storage</string>
    <string name="day_4_des">Invest in an SSD of at least 500GB for your operating system to be installed on, leaving room for some of your favorite games, too. HDDs are often cheaper and offer more storage for the money, but SSDs are faster and better for performance.</string>
    <string name="day_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day_5_title">Next-Gen Storage</string>
    <string name="day_5_des">If you want to get one step ahead, NVMe SSDs offer faster data transfer rates compared to SSDs. However, you will need to check how many PCIe slots your motherboard has (if any).</string>
    <string name="day_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day_6_title">Immersive Gaming Experience</string>
    <string name="day_6_des">For the ultimate gaming PC setup, you\'ll want to get at least a 24-inch monitor. 1080p monitors are great, and you won\'t need such strong hardware, but a 4K monitor (3840x2160) with 144Hz refresh rate will offer the best experience for AAA titles.</string>
    <string name="day_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day_7_title">Keep your Rig Cool</string>
    <string name="day_7_des">Gaming PCs tend to be performance-intensive. This means you\'ll need to ensure your PC has adequate cooling to keep temperatures low while gaming. Fans are great and do the job well, but you can go for liquid cooling if you want it to look fancy.</string>
    <string name="day_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day_8_title">Memory Match</string>
    <string name="day_8_des">When purchasing RAM for your PC, make sure it\'s compatible with your motherboard. Most new motherboards will offer support for DDR4, and some even go as far as DDR5.</string>
    <string name="day_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day_9_title">Dual-Channel Power</string>
    <string name="day_9_des">8GB RAM is the absolute minimum you should look at when building or upgrading your PC. However, in most cases, it\'s just as affordable to double up to 16GB RAM. Two sticks of RAM are also better than one since they offer dual-channel memory slots.</string>
    <string name="day_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day_10_title">Power Your Setup</string>
    <string name="day_10_des">All of the hardware in your PC needs power, and therefore you need a PSU to support all of your components. It\'s recommended to get an 80 Plus Gold or an 80 Plus Platinum PSU for better power efficiency. You can also use a PSU calculator to determine what wattage you require.</string>
    <string name="day_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day_11_title">Light Up your Rig</string>
    <string name="day_11_des">In addition to performance, a gaming PC should stand out from the crowd. RGB lighting strips and RGB fans are an affordable way to make your case look awesome.</string>
    <string name="day_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day_12_title">Organized Gaming Space</string>
    <string name="day_12_des">If you\'re adding a lot of peripherals to your gaming PC, you\'ll notice the abundance of wires and cables cluttering up your desk. Gaming desks are built specifically to offer cable management and often can be adjusted to the right height.</string>
    <string name="day_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day_13_title">Precision and Style</string>
    <string name="day_13_des">Mechanical keyboards are often favored by PC gamers. That\'s because they offer low actuation (travel distance), responsive keys, and hotkeys that are useful when playing games.</string>
    <string name="day_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day_14_title">Find Your Feel</string>
    <string name="day_14_des">Decide whether you want to opt for linear, tactile, or clicky switches on your keyboard. Linear switches tend to be smoother, while tactile and clicky offer confirmation in the sound and feel of the keys when pressed.</string>
    <string name="day_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day_15_title">Control Your Game</string>
    <string name="day_15_des">An adjustable DPI gaming mouse should be considered in order to receive accurate response times and mouse clicks. For MMO or competitive gamers, a mouse with programmable buttons is essential.</string>
    <string name="day_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day_16_title">Versatile Input</string>
    <string name="day_16_des">Although a mouse and keyboard are necessary for most PC gaming setups, many games also support game controllers, including the Xbox Series X controller.</string>
    <string name="day_17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day_17_title">Keep It Tidy</string>
    <string name="day_17_des">Keeping your gaming desk tidy and free from clutter is vital. There are plenty of gaming accessories that can help with this, including an extended mouse pad, headphone stands, and a USB hub.</string>
    <string name="day_18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day_18_title">Ergonomic Comfort</string>
    <string name="day_18_des">Although your PC will be the bread and butter of your gaming setup, it\'s important to consider comfort, especially when playing for long hours. A robust chair needs to be considered, especially one offers height adjustment, 4D armrests, and tilt.</string>
    <string name="day_19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day_19_title">Immersive Audio</string>
    <string name="day_19_des">Some gaming monitors including built-in speakers, but these are often low wattage and won\'t feel particularly immersive. PC gaming brands like HyperX, Corsair, and SteelSeries offer incredible gaming headsets.</string>
    <string name="day_20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day_20_title">Sound and Voice Clarity</string>
    <string name="day_20_des">If you\'re planning to go down the speaker route and want to communicate with your friends, you can invest in a separate speaker and microphone set up.</string>
    <string name="day_21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day_21_title">Stream Like a Pro</string>
    <string name="day_21_des">Many PC gamers also enjoy streaming, so it\'s important to look at microphone set-ups that cater to this. Additional accessories like a boom arm and pop filter can be useful to dampen background noise and make your microphone more accessible.</string>
    <string name="day_22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day_22_title">Streamline Your Streaming</string>
    <string name="day_22_des">If you\'re a keen streamer, hardware like Stream Deck could make switching between streaming sites and programs much simpler.</string>
    <string name="day_23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day_23_title">Choose your Platform</string>
    <string name="day_23_des">Steam is by far the most popular platform to explore and purchase new games. However, there are other options like Epic Store, GOG Galaxy, Ubisoft Connect, and so on.</string>
    <string name="day_24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day_24_title">Find your Match</string>
    <string name="day_24_des">If you\'re trying to find the best game to play that caters for your needs, make sure you filter games by type, e.g. Co-op, MMO, FPS, RTS, etc. This will make it easier to search through a library of games.</string>
    <string name="day_25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day_25_title">Risk-Free Gaming</string>
    <string name="day_25_des">Purchased a game via Steam that is full of issues or doesn\'t work? Steam offers refunds on games if you\'ve played them for less than two hours, within two weeks of purchase.</string>
    <string name="day_26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day_26_title">Connect with Gamers</string>
    <string name="day_26_des">oin a Reddit community for your favorite games to learn new tips and tricks, or join a subreddit to explore different gaming communities and learn new things.</string>
    <string name="day_27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day_27_title">Ultimate Wi-Fi Experience</string>
    <string name="day_27_des">Choose a high-end router that offers Wi-Fi 6, like the TP-Link Archer AX11000. Not only does it offer features like a gamer-centric interface, it\'s extremely powerful and supports Wi-Fi 6.</string>
    <string name="day_28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day_28_title">Network Match</string>
    <string name="day_28_des">Ensure your network card is compatible with your router. For example, if your network card doesn\'t support Wi-Fi 6, you may need to reconsider your options.</string>
    <string name="day_29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day_29_title">Wired or Wireless</string>
    <string name="day_29_des">Deciding between a Wi-Fi and Ethernet connection for gaming can be confusing. While Wi-Fi has substantially improved, nothing compares to connecting your PC directly to your router via an Ethernet connection.</string>
    <string name="day_30">Day 30</string>
    <string name="day_30_title">Boost Your Connection</string>
    <string name="day_30_des">If you can\'t connect via Ethernet, you should ensure you can connect to the 5GHz band on your router. The range won\'t extend as far, but your performance will drastically increase over the 2.4GHz band.</string>
</resources>